

# RODRIGO GALDINO

RUBY ON RAILS DEVELOPER ♥ SÃO JOÃO DO PARAÍSO, BRAZIL \$\circ{\circ} +5538997324227

## • DETAILS •

São João do Paraíso Brazil +5538997324227 galdinorodrigo553@gmail.com

## · LINKS ·

My portfolio

<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Linkedin</u>

#### o SKILLS o

Ruby on Rails

JavaScript

HTML & CSS

jQuery

SQL

PostgreSQL

MySQL

Git

**Automated Testing** 

RSpec

Heroku

Docker

Amazon AWS

LANGUAGES

Portuguese

English

#### PROFILE

Self thought Ruby on rails Developer. I study computing on my own since I was 14 years old, I learned many things about solving problems that made me more motivated to learn more and solve more. I love how in my hands I can build a system that other people can use, and be helpful

# EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

#### Ruby on rails junior developer at Freelancer, São João do Paraíso

May 2021 — December 2022

I have worked as a freelancer to some costumers as a rails developer, but I keep a strong contract with one in specific, I was responsible to build new features and fix existent features in his applications, in this job I worked with many technologies beside of ruby on rails, like amazon AWS, heroku, docker, web marketing campaigns services, front end technologies like HTML, CSS, JavaScript, view component, tailwind, and several APIs...

## Freelancer frontend developer at freelancer, São João do Paraíso

August 2020 - April 2021

I was starting to earn my first money by coding, I subscribed in some freelancers platforms and got some jobs with HTML, CSS and JavaScript, I worked adding new features and fixing existent websites from several different costumers

## Ruby on rails developer at esense care, São João do Paraíso

August 2022 — Present

I'm responsible to maintain an existing ruby on rails application, I have to fix existing features and create new features for the application that is a platform used for several users in Brasil.

# EDUCATION

Tecnólogo em Análise e Desenvolvimento de Sistemas, Unopar, São João do Paraíso July 2021 — July 2023

My degree is a Brazilian model, it's focused to prepare the professional to labor market, so it's focused in to teach us things that will let us ready to jobs in 2 years, so we learn many things that we'll need to work in companies

# COURSES

Ruby on Rails - Introdução a arquitetura MVC, Digital Innovation One November 2021 — December 2021

Ruby on Rails 6: Learn 25+ gems and build a Startup MVP 2022, Udemy October 2022 — Present

Construindo páginas para internet com Bootstrap, Digital Innovation One

November 2020 — November 2020